workingsol.com 2018-10-03

# Privacy | Working Solutions

### **WSOL, LLC Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy sets out how WSOL, LLC uses and protects any information that you give when using this website.

WSOL, LLC is committed to protecting your privacy. If we ask you to provide certain information from which you can be identified when using this site, you can be assured it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

WSOL, LLC may change the policy by updating this page. You should check it from time to time to ensure that you are alright with any changes. This policy is effective from 4/1/2016.

### **What’s Collected**

We may collect the following information:

  * Name and job title
  * Contact information, including email address
  * Demographic information—such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### **What We Do with It**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide better service. This includes:

  * Internal record keeping
  * Information to improve our products and services
  * Promotional emails, special offers or other information, using the email address you provided
  * Market research purposes via email, phone, fax or mail
  * Website customization, according to your interests
  * Marketing or promotional purposes from our third-party partners

We will never sell your information.

### **Security**

We are committed to ensuring your information is secure. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we are have in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard information collected online.

### **How We Use Cookies**

A cookie is a small file that asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added. The cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site.

Cookies enable web applications to respond to you as an individual. An application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic-log cookies to identify which pages are used. This helps us analyze data about web-page traffic and improve our site, tailoring it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes. The data then is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor the pages you find useful or not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. You can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies, if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### **Links to Other Sites**

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other sites. Once you leave our website and use the links, be aware we do not have any control over them.

Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you provide while visiting such sites. They are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and review their privacy statements.

### **Controlling Personal Information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * When you are asked to fill out a form on the website, look for the box you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct-marketing purposes.
  * If you have agreed for us to use your information for direct marketing, you may change your mind at any time by emailing to marketing@workingsol.com.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may use this information to send you promotional information about third parties, which we think you may find interesting, but only if you agree.

You may request details of personal information we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy, please write us at 1820 Preston Park Blvd., Suite 2000, Plano, TX 75093.

If you believe any information we about you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any wrong information.
